{
    "id": "182795d17a2a438ea49724feb6a1ae27",
    "title": "While And During",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I met a nice French girl ……………….. my stay in Switzerland.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "while",
                "during"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "7bccd5a3e28f422dbb7b9129d047c732"
        },
        {
            "question": "……………… I was holidaying in Switzerland, I met a nice French girl.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "While",
                "During"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "b1f502b7adba4e7bbb9f9451a6bc9e69"
        },
        {
            "question": "I learned some Russian ………………. I was studying in Russia.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "while",
                "during"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "f5980d5ea43143449f1ebce983393d17"
        },
        {
            "question": "We can meet ………………. lunchtime.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "during",
                "while"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "e1e4c863745b4889bb85250094908980"
        },
        {
            "question": "It happened ………………. I was working in the garden.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "while",
                "during"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "d976c90b272c4417b2abbeb1570ca6dd"
        },
        {
            "question": "I was in hospital ………………… the winter.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "while",
                "during"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "0aa590db24014e9e9b4dd438116dead9"
        },
        {
            "question": "The shop was closed ……………….. the whole of March.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "during",
                "while"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "00f63e6fadb24e98a0bcdfa9ef6da084"
        },
        {
            "question": "I had some strange experiences ………………. working in France.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "while",
                "during"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "5a852d91b96a40409eedf423513110ed"
        },
        {
            "question": "I woke up ……………….. the night.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "while",
                "during"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "3914e9672987420b8c89991ebdb7628b"
        },
        {
            "question": "I cooked dinner ………………. Samuel watched TV.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "during",
                "while"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "46015b4fea0d494ea643140ba4350a98"
        }
    ]
}